Guide to the Bates Worldwide, Inc. Records, 1934-2005 and undated RL.00090
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Corporate Communications Department Series, 1940-2003 and undated, 115 boxes
  - Offices Subseries, 1979-2001 and undated
    - Headquarters
      - Backer Spielvogel Bates (BSB)
        - Slides of company events
          - Moving in/unpacking, undated (Box CC80)
      - Bates USA
        - Headquarters move
          - General, 1996-1999, 3 folders (Box CC80)
          - Chrysler Building, undated (Box CC80)
          - Communications plan--Team 498, 1998 (Box CC80)
          - Final Studios report, 1997-1998 (Box CC80)
          - Photographs of new offices, 1999 Feb. 4 (Box CC80)
          - Press clippings, 1996-1999, 3 folders (Box CC80A)
          - Time capsule, 1998 (Box CC81)
          - Transition team, 1998, 2 folders (Box CC81)
          - Website, 1998 (Box CC81)
        - Press clippings, 1991-2001, Folders 1-6 of 28 (Box CC81)
        - Press clippings, 1991-2001 (continued), Folders 7-22 of 28 (Box CC82)
        - Press clippings, 1991-2001 (continued), Folders 23-28 of 28 (Box CC83)
      - Bates Worldwide
        - Highlights and Biographical updates, 1979-2000, 2 folders (Box CC83)
        - Press clippings, 1991-2001, Folders 1-8 of 15 (Box CC83)
        - Press clippings, 1991-2001 (continued), Folders 9-15 of 15 (Box CC84)
      - Cordiant Communications Group (CCG)
        - Annual and interim reports
          - 1994-1998 (Box CC84)
          - 1998-2001 (Box CC85)
        - Board meeting, 1998 (Box CC85)
        - Going Forward, 1998 (Box CC85)
        - Memoranda and miscellaneous, 1998-2001, Folders 1-4 of 7 (Box CC85)
        - Memoranda and miscellaneous, 1998-2001 (continued), Folders 5-7 of 7 (Box CC86)
        - Year-end results, 1999 Mar. (Box CC86)
      - Saatchi & Saatchi
        - Annual and preliminary reports, 1988-1993 (Box CC86)
        - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box CC86)
    - International offices, 1985-2001
      - Asia-Pacific, 1987-2001
        - General (Bates Asia-Pacific), 1988-2000 (Box CC86)
        - Australia
          - Campaign Palace, 1992-1998 (Box CC86)
          - George Patterson Bates, 1989-2001, 4 folders (Box CC87)
        - China (Backer Spielvogel Bates), 1992-2000 (Box CC87)
        - Hong Kong (Bates), 1990-2001, 3 folders (Box CC87)
        - India (Clarion), 1997-2000, 2 folders (Box CC87)
        - Japan (Bates), 1988-2000, 4 folders (Box CC87)
        - Korea (Bates Diamond Ad), 1988-2000, 2 folders (Box CC88)
        - Malaysia, 1987-1994, 2 folders (Box CC88)
        - New Zealand
          - Bates, 1990-1994, 3 folders (Box CC88)
          - Campaign Palace, 2000 (Box CC88)
        - Singapore (Bates), 1987-2001, 3 folders (Box CC88)
        - Thailand (Bates), 1989-1992 (Box CC88)
        - Taiwan (Bates), 1987-1992, 2 folders (Box CC88)
        - Vietnam (Bates Vinexad), 1993-1998, 3 folders (Box CC88)
      - Europe, 1985-2001
        - General (Bates Europe), 1991-2000, 4 folders (Box CC88)
        - Austria (Dr. Puttner Bates), 1988-2000, 2 folders (Box CC88)
        - Belgium (Bates), 1985-2000, 2 folders (Box CC89)
        - Denmark (Bates), 1987-1998, 2 folders (Box CC89)
        - Eastern Block Countries, 1991-1993 (Box CC89)
        - Finland (Bates S & S Finland Oy), 1987-1994, 3 folders (Box CC89)
        - France
          - Backer Spielvogel Bates, 1988 (Box CC89)
          - Bates, 1989-2001, 3 folders (Box CC89)
        - Germany
          - General, 1998-2000 (Box CC89)
          - Frankfurt, 1994-1998, 2 folders (Box CC89)
          - Scholz and Friends, 1991-1998, 3 folders (Box CC89)
        - Greece (Bates Hellas), 1986-1992, 2 folders (Box CC90)
        - Hungary, 1992-1997 (Box CC90)
        - Ireland (Bates), 1992-1998, 3 folders (Box CC90)
        - Italy (Bates Italia), 1987-2001, 3 folders (Box CC90)
        - Netherlands (Allick Bates), 1987-1994, 2 folders (Box CC90)
        - Norway (Bates Gruppen), 1987-2001, 3 folders (Box CC90)
        - Poland (Bates), 1992-1994 (Box CC90)
        - Portugal 1987, 2000, 2 folders (Box CC90)
        - Russia (Bates), 1986-1996, 2 folders (Box CC90)
        - Spain, 1987-2001, 3 folders (Box CC90)
        - Sweden (Bates September), 1987-1989, 2 folders (Box CC90)
        - Switzerland (Zogg. Kittiger), 1987 (Box CC90)
        - Turkey, 1992 (Box CC90)
        - United Kingdom (Bates Dorland), 1988-2001, 8 folders (Box CC91)
      - Latin America, 1991-2000
        - General (Bates Latin America), 1993-2001, 6 folders (Box CC92)
        - Argentina, 1994-2000, 4 folders (Box CC92)
        - Brazil, 1998, 6 folders (Box CC93)
        - Chile, 1999 (Box CC93)
        - Colombia, 1995-1997 and undated, 3 folders (Box CC93)
        - Costa Rica, 1998 (Box CC93)
        - Dominican Republic, 1998 (Box CC93)
        - Ecuador, 1991-1993 (Box CC93)
        - El Salvador, 1999 (Box CC93)
        - Guatemala, 1998-1999 (Box CC93)
        - Mexico, 1997-1998 and undated, 2 folders (Box CC93)
        - Panama, 1998 (Box CC93)
        - Peru, 1998 and undated (Box CC93)
        - Puerto Rico, 1999 (Box CC94)
        - Venezuela, 1988-1999, 2 folders (Box CC94)
      - Middle East and Africa, 1987-2001
        - Nigeria, 1987-1992, 2 folders (Box CC94)
        - Pan-Gulf, 1999-2000 (Box CC94)
        - South Africa (Bates), 1990-2001, 2 folders (Box CC94)
    - North American offices, 1989-2001
      - Regional Offices, 1991-2001
        - General (Bates North America), 1994-2001, 4 folders (Box CC94)
        - Canada (Bates), 1989-2001, 3 folders (Box CC94)
        - Manhattan (Bates), 1991-1995, 2 folders (Box CC94)
        - Midwest (Bates USA), 1992-2001, 4 folders (Box CC95)
        - South (Bates USA), 1994-2001, 4 folders (Box CC95)
        - Southwest (Bates USA), 1995-2001, Folder 1 of 3 (Box CC95)
        - Southwest (Bates USA), 1995-2001, Folders 2-3 of 3 (Box CC96)
        - West (Bates USA), 1994-2000, 6 folders (Box CC96)
      - Subsidiaries, 1989-2001
        - 141 Interactive, 1999-2003, 8 folders
          - Disk 14. Live at Life event (Box CC96)
        - AC & R Agencies - Alliance, Manhattan, Holdings, 1991-1995, 2 folders (Box CC97)
        - Bates Alliance, 1989-1995, 2 folders (Box CC97)
        - Bates Communications, 1997-1998 (Box CC97)
        - Bates Direct, 1995, 2 folders (Box CC97)
        - Bates Entertainment/BKS, 1995-1999, 7 folders (Box CC97)
        - Bates Healthcom, 1997, 2 folders (Box CC97)
        - Bates Holdings, 1992-1994, 2 folders (Box CC97)
        - Bates Travel and Tourism (Atlanta), 1999-2001 (Box CC97)
        - CCG.XM, 2000, 2 folders (Box CC98)
        - Zenith
          - General information, undated (Box CC98)
          - Press clippings, 1994-2001, 9 folders (Box CC98)
  - People Subseries, 1940-2001 and undated
    Clippings, press releases, photographs, biographical sketches, writings, speeches and presentations relating primarily to Bates executives, but also includes files on key corporate leaders and other prominent people. There are no employment-related materials present apart from publicly released notices of appointments and promotions, and biographical materials gathered for use in public releases and internal newsletter items. Organized alphabetically.
    - Achenbaum, Alvin A. (Box CC99)
      - By-lined articles
        - Advertising Age, 1989 (Box CC99)
        - Adweek, 1985-1986 (Box CC99)
        - Adweek's Marketing Week, 1986-1988 (Box CC99)
      - Speeches
        - Advertising Environment of the Nineties, 1992 Apr. 27 (Box CC99)
        - Compensation Philosophy: The Client View, 1989 Oct. 17 (Box CC99)
        - How I Would Select an Advertising Agency, 1988 Feb. 22 (Box CC99)
        - Transformation of the Packaged Food Environment, 1990 Jan. (Box CC99)
    - Aminoff, Susan, 1998 May 28 (Box CC99)
      Includes notice of promotion to Senior Vice President.
    - Aroyan, Edward, 2000 May 15 (Box CC99)
      Includes notice of promotion to Executive Vice President.
    - Assumma, Frank
      - Association of National Advertisers (A.N.A.) speech, 1995 Feb. 1
        - General (Box CC99)
        - Assumma's speech and audiovisual cues (Box CC99)
        - Press release (Box CC99)
        - Slides (Box CC99)
      - BKS/Bates Entertainment Group Photo (Box CC99)
      - Banking syndicate meeting, 1994 Nov. 11 (Box CC99)
      - Discount store news, 1994 Oct. 20 (Box CC99)
      - Named CEO of BSB (Backer Spielvogel Bates), Inc., 1994 Jan. 18 (Box CC99)
      - Press clippings, 1991-1994 (Box CC100)
    - Artzet, Edwin L.
      CEO of Proctor and Gamble.
      - The Future of Advertising, 1994 (Box CC100)
      - Grooming the Next Generation of Management, 1991 (Box CC100)
    - Avery, Graham, 1999 Oct. 5 (Box CC100)
      Includes notice of appointment as President and CEO of Bates Canada.
    - Backer, Bill
      - Biographical information, undated (Box CC100)
      - Photographs, 1989, 3 folders (Box CC100)
      - Press clippings, 1989-1994 (Box CC100)
    - Baldwin, Joanna, 1998 Apr. 28 (Box CC100)
      Bates Europe.
    - Basile, Paul
      See related materials in file for Jim McKennan.
      - Biographical information, undated (Box CC100)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC100)
    - Bassell, Gary
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC100)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC100)
      - Promoted to senior Vice President, General Manager at Bates USA South in Miami, 1997 Aug. 7 (Box CC100)
      - Press clippings, 1997-2001 (Box CC100)
    - Bates, Theodore, 1940-1982
      - General, 1940-1982 (Box CC100)
      - Biographical information, 1992 (Box CC100)
      - History, 1994 (Box CC100)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1979 (Box CC100)
      - Photographs, 1986-2000, 2 folders (Box CC100)
    - Bendelac, Stanley
      - General, 1995-1997 (Box CC100)
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC100)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC100)
      - Press releases
        - Appointed CEO of Bates Europe, 1996 Nov. 21 (Box CC100)
        - Named to additional post as Regional Director of Bates Latin America, 1997 Nov. 11 (Box CC100)
    - Bennett, Steve, New Media and the Travel Industry, 1995 (Box CC100)
    - Bescoby, Janet
      - Named Senior Vice President, Media Direct, Bates USA West, 2000 Apr. 17 (Box CC100)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC100)
    - Bradley, Stephanie, 1992 (Box CC101)
    - Browne, Noel, 1996 June 7 (Box CC101)
      Bates New Zealand.
    - Bungey, Michael
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC101)
      - By-lined articles, 1993-1997 (Box CC101)
      - Photographs, 1993-2000, 3 folders (Box CC101)
      - Press clippings, 1988-2001, 3 folders (Box CC101)
      - Press releases
        - Named President and Chief Operations Officer of BSBW (Backer Spielvogel Bates Worldwide), 1992 Nov. 4 (Box CC101)
        - Named CEO of BSBW, 1993 (Box CC101)
      - Speeches
        - American Advertising Federation (AAF), The Wonder of One to One, 1995, Folder 1 of 3
          - Disk 4. Program files (Box CC101)
            Disk contains program file entitled 1 To 1 and supporting files
        - American Advertising Federation (AAF), The Wonder of One to One, 1995 (continued), Folders 2-3 of 3 (Box CC102)
        - Argentine Advertising Association, 1993 Oct. 12 (Box CC102)
        - Conference Board (Human Resources), 1993 Oct. 15 (Box CC102)
        - Conference Board Marketing Conference, 1993 Oct. 26, 5 folders (Box CC102)
        - Cordiant annual meeting, London bankers, 1995 June 14 (Box CC102)
        - European Managers Meeting, Building a Global Brand, 1994 Apr., 3 folders (Box CC103)
        - International Advertising Association (IAA)
          - Interactive Consumer
            Speech given at various IAA functions.
            - Austria, 1996 Apr. 23, 2 folders (Box CC103)
            - India (Bombay), 1996 June 4 (Box CC103)
            - Korea (Seoul), 1996 June 10 (Box CC103)
            - New York, N.Y., 1994 Sept. 19 (Box CC103)
          - World Advertising Congress, 1994, 3 folders (Box CC104)
        - New York agency meeting at Hunter College, 1993 Jun. 6 (Box CC104)
        - South Africa
          - Financial Mail Speech, 1997, 2 folders (Box CC104)
          - Welcoming remarks, Bates South Africa launch, 1994 (Box CC104)
        - Summit '94: The National Conference on Agency Growth and Client Retention, 1994 May 20, Folders 1-2 of 3 (Box CC104)
        - Summit '94: The National Conference on Agency Growth and Client Retention, 1994 May 20 (continued), Folder 3 of 3 (Box CC105)
        - Wendy's International, Think Big, 1994 Oct. 24 (Box CC105)
        - Worldwide Management Meeting (WWMM), 1993 May 18, 2 folders (Box CC105)
        - Year-end message, 1997 Jan. 20 (Box CC105)
        - Miscellaneous speeches, 1991-1996 (Box CC105)
    - Butt, Richard (Box CC106)
      - Biographical information, undated (Box CC106)
      - Photo, undated (Box CC106)
    - Caffera, John
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC106)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC106)
      - Promoted to Senior Vice President, Director of Broadcast Production, 1997 Aug. 7 (Box CC106)
    - Caggiano, Tom, 1997 July 15 (Box CC106)
      Includes notice of promotion to Senior Vice President and Creative Director, Bates USA.
    - Carpenter, Tom, 1999 Mar. 15 (Box CC106)
      Vice President, 141 Interactive.
    - Citron, John
      - General, undated (Box CC106)
      - BSB/Ghersy/Quintero reception speech, 1990 Oct. 22 (Box CC106)
    - Clark, Chris
      - Appointed Director of Business Development, Bates North America, 1999 Apr. 30 (Box CC106)
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC106)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC106)
    - Clinton, William (Bill), Democratic National Convention speech, 1992 (Box CC106)
    - Common, William
      - Joins 141 USA as senior Vice President, Business Development, the Americas, 1997 Oct. 2 (Box CC106)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC106)
    - Corrigan, Tim
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC106)
      - General, 1993 and undated, 2 folders (Box CC106)
      - Photographs, 2000, 3 folders (Box CC106)
      - Speeches
        - European American Chamber of Commerce (EACC) speech, 1993 Oct. 21 (Box CC106)
        - NY meeting at Hunter College, 1993 June 25 (Box CC106)
        - Ten Steps to Marketing in New Europe, 1994 Sept. (Box CC106)
    - Courtemanche, Howard
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC106)
      - Photographs, 2000, 2 folders (Box CC106)
      - Press Releases
        - Joins Bates USA as senior Vice President, Management Rep on Warner-Lambert, 1997 Mar. 19 (Box CC106)
        - Promoted to Executive Vice President at Bates USA, 1998 June 2 (Box CC106)
    - Coyne, Kevin
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC106)
      - General, 2001 (Box CC106)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC106)
      - Press Releases
        - Promoted to Executive Vice President, Bates USA West, 1997 Feb. 12 (Box CC106)
        - Promoted to Executive Vice President, Director of Media and New Technology, 1998 (Box CC106)
    - Cracknell, Andrew (Box CC107)
      See related material in files for Frank Assumma.
      - Appointed Executive Creative Director at Bates UK, 1999 Sept. 29 (Box CC107)
      - Biographical information, 1994 (Box CC107)
      - Photographs, 1994 (Box CC107)
    - D'Angelo, Art
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC107)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC107)
      - Press Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box CC107)
      - Press Releases
        - Named Chief Finance Officer of BSB (Backer Spielvogel Bates), Epstein leaves as Chief Finance Officer of BSB (Backer Spielvogel Bates), 1994 Mar. 18 (Box CC107)
        - Named Chief Finance Officer of Bates Worldwide, 1995 July 12 (Box CC107)
    - Debreceni, John, 2000 (Box CC107)
    - Denehy, Micky, 1999 Sept. 21 (Box CC107)
      Includes notice of promotion to New Business Director for Bates Europe.
    - de Yturbe, Jean: see Yturbe, Jean de (Box CC107)
    - Dolan, Bernie, 1997 Feb. 26 (Box CC107)
      Includes notice of appointment as Chief Finance Officer, Bates North America.
    - Dudynskay, N. Michael, 1999 Feb. 16 (Box CC107)
      Includes notice of promotion to Regional Managing Director of Bates Latin America.
    - Easdon, Don
      - Speeches
        - Advertising Age Creative Workshop, 1991 Aug. 22 (Box CC107)
        - Boston Creative Conference, 1992 May 21 (Box CC107)
    - Eazor, Joe
      - Appointed CEO for Interactive Businesses at CCG (Cordiant Communications Group), 1999 Aug. 13 (Box CC107)
      - Photographs, undated (Box CC107)
    - Fawcett, John
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC107)
      - Photographs, 1996-2000, 3 folders (Box CC107)
      - Press clippings, 1999-2001, 2 folders (Box CC107)
    - Froelich, Bob
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC107)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC107)
    - Gamble, Robert, 2000 (Box CC107)
    - Grignon, Perianne, 1997 Oct. 3 (Box CC107)
      Includes notice of promotion to Executive Vice President, Director of New Media and New Technologies, Bates North America.
    - Hackett, Randall
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC107)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC107)
    - Hahn, Carole, undated (Box CC107)
    - Hamill, Alex
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC107)
      - Photographs, 2000-1991, 2 folders (Box CC107)
      - Speeches (Ad Pride program), 1992 (Box CC108)
    - Hamilton, Rich, undated (Box CC108)
      Zenith Media.
    - Hart, Timothy
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC108)
      - Named President and CEO of Bates USA West, 1996 Dec. 18 (Box CC108)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC108)
    - Hearn, Colin, 2000 (Box CC108)
    - Hinton, Graham, 2000 (Box CC108)
    - Kahn, Dominique Bigar, 2000 Mar. 7 (Box CC108)
      Includes notice of promotion to Senior Vice President, Creative Manager for Bates USA.
    - Kapsky, Mark, 1996 May 1 (Box CC108)
      Vice President, Director of Client Services, Bates Promotion Group, Bates USA.
    - Kaszner, Charles, 2000 (Box CC108)
    - Kellam, Alan, 2000 (Box CC108)
    - Kennedy, Neil, British Supermarket Image War, 1992 Jan. 31 (Box CC108)
    - Knisley, Patrick
      - Appointed President and Chief Operations Officer of Bates Canada, 1996 Oct. 15 (Box CC108)
      - Biographical information, 1992-1996 (Box CC108)
      - Photographs, undated (Box CC108)
    - Kost, Steve, 2001 (Box CC108)
    - Lazarus, Kara
      - General, 1998-2001, 2 folders (Box CC108)
      - Promoted to Senior Vice President, Director of National Broadcast Buying Group at Bates USA, 2001 Apr. 3 (Box CC108)
    - Lazarus, Shelley, Positioning the Agency as A Brand, 1997 (Box CC108)
    - Levine, Paul
      - Appointed Executive Vice President, Chief Marketing Officer Bates North America, 1999 Dec.6 (Box CC108)
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC108)
      - Photographs, 2000, 2 folders
        - Disk 15. Photograph on Zip disk. (Box CC108)
    - Marchese, John
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC108)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC108)
      - Joins Bates USA as Executive Vice President, Director of Marketing and Development, 1996 Oct. 4 (Box CC108)
      - Speeches, 1999 (Box CC108)
    - Mazzuchelli, Robert
      - Biographical information, 1997 (Box CC108)
      - Photographs, undated (Box CC108)
    - McBride, Gary (Box CC109)
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC109)
      - Named President Latin America, to lead expansion effort, 2000 June 7 (Box CC109)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC109)
    - McKennan, Jim/ Paul Basile, 1993-2001 (Box CC109)
    - Melanson, Anne, 1991
      - Appointed to Bates Worldwide Management Board, 1996 Apr. 9 (Box CC109)
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC109)
      - Bylines, 1991 (Box CC109)
      - Photographs, 2000, 2 folders (Box CC109)
    - Morris, Mark
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC109)
      - Photographs, 2000, 2 folders (Box CC109)
    - Newman, Richard
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC109)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC109)
    - Osborn, Rick, undated (Box CC109)
    - Papagiannacopoulos, Yannis, undated (Box CC109)
    - Person, Sarah, 1995 Mar. 10 (Box CC109)
      Vice President, Editorial Director, Corporate Communications, Bates USA.
    - Pironen, Maria
      - Biographical information, undated (Box CC109)
      - Photographs, undated (Box CC109)
    - Pond-Jones, Jay, undated (Box CC109)
    - Potenzano, John
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC109)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC109)
    - Puttner, Gerhard, 2000 (Box CC109)
    - Reeves, Rosser
      - Archival and bibliographic information (Box CC109)
        Concerns Rosser Reeves Papers at the State Historical Society of Wisconsin.
      - American Advertising Federation Hall of Fame research, 1994 (Box CC109)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC109)
      - Press clippings, 1955-1996, 3 folders (Box CC110)
      - Reality in Advertising, 1951-1996, 2 folders (Box CC110)
      - Research, 1991-2003 (Box CC110)
      - Writings and speeches, 1959-1966, 2 folders (Box CC110)
    - David Reyburn, 2000 (Box CC111)
    - Robertson, Mike, 1995-1999
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC111)
      - Photographs, 2000, 2 folders (Box CC111)
      - Press Clippings, 1995-1999 (Box CC111)
      - Press Releases
        - Named Executive Vice President, Executive Creative Director Bates USA, 1995 Apr. 21 (Box CC111)
        - Appoints 3 New Creatives at Bates USA West, 2000 July 18 (Box CC111)
    - Roman, Dan, 2000 (Box CC111)
    - Sanson-Tricard, Violaine, 2000 (Box CC111)
    - Scaros, Dean, Advertising's Not So Secret War, 1990 May 8 (Box CC111)
    - Schoenfeld, Jay
      - General, 1990-1994 (Box CC111)
      - Recession advertising background information, 1991 Jan. 4 (Box CC111)
    - Schoning, Peter, 2000 (Box CC111)
    - Schweitzer, Gerry
      - Biographical information, 2001 (Box CC111)
      - Photographs, 2001 (Box CC111)
    - Silberberg, Bob
      - Biographical information, 1991 (Box CC111)
      - Photographs, undated (Box CC111)
      - Press Clippings, 1991-1995 (Box CC111)
    - Silver, Jackie, ESOMAR conference speech, 1990 (Box CC111)
    - Silverman, Marylin
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC111)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC111)
      - Speech, Japanese Chamber of Commerce, 1992 Apr. 27 (Box CC111)
    - Singer, Claude
      - Biographical information, undated (Box CC111)
      - Joins CCG.XM as Chief Marketing Officer, 2000 Mar. 17 (Box CC111)
      - Photographs, undated (Box CC111)
    - Slosberg, Robert (Box CC112)
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC112)
      - Joins Bates USA as Executive Vice President, Group Creative Director, 2001 Feb. 12 (Box CC112)
      - Photographs, 2000 (Box CC112)
    - Smith, Ian
      - Appointed President, International Bates Worldwide, 1998 Feb. 10 (Box CC112)
      - Biographical information, 2000 (Box CC112)
      - ESPN Conference Board, 2000 Mar., 2 folders (Box CC112)
      - Photographs, undated (Box CC112)
    - Smith, Nancy, undated (Box CC112)
    - Spielvogel, Carl
      - Biographical Information, undated (Box CC112)
      - Go, South America presentation, 1991 (Box CC112)
      - Photographs, undated (Box CC112)
      - Press Clippings, 1988-1993 (Box CC112)
    - Stake, Marcus H., 1999 Sept. 30 (Box CC112)
      Includes notice of appointment as CEO of 141 Europe.
    - Steele, Gary
      - ANA (Association of National Advertisers), 1996 Oct. (Box CC112)
      - Biographical Information, 1999 (Box CC112)
      - Photographs, undated (Box CC112)
    - Stern, Les, undated (Box CC112)
    - Stone, Marcia
      - Photographs, 2000, 2 folders (Box CC112)
      - Press Releases
        - Joins Bates USA Midwest as Executive Vice President, Creative Director, 1996 June 12 (Box CC112)